packagemapping.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Notice

Thank you for reading this Privacy Notice. This notice applies ONLY to information collected or provided when visiting www.PackageMapping.com public web site or using E-mail. This notice covers the following topics: 

  * Information collected and how it is used
  * Personal information and choice
  * Cookies and Applets
  * Security
  * Disclaimer
  * Copyright
  * Contact Information

**__

__

**

**Information collected and how it is used**

#### What information is collected when you browse this site?

When you browse or download information from this site, some information is gathered about **** your **** visit. This information does not identify you personally, and is used only to help improve this site. The information is never made available for commercial use. The following information is automatically collected each time you visit: 

  1. The Internet Protocol (IP) Address and domain name used. The IP Address is a numerical identifier assigned either to your Internet service provider or directly to your computer. The IP Address helps direct Internet traffic to you. 
  2. The type of browser and operating system you used. 
  3. The date and time you visited this site. 
  4. The Internet pages or services you visited at this site. 
  5. The Internet site you visited before coming to this site. 

****

**What information is collected if you volunteer it**?

If you send an E-mail, participate in an online survey, or provide other information using this site, the following may also be collected: 

  1. Your E-mail address and contents of your E-mail message (including attachments and signature blocks). 
  2. Contact information (address, telephone). 
  3. Organization that you represent. 
  4. Information volunteered in response to a survey. 
  5. Information volunteered through an on-line form for any other purpose. 
  6. Any tracking numbers entered into the Tracking Program.

The information collected is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video and graphic information formats you choose to send. 

Your E-mail address is used to answer your questions, address your concerns, or forward to someone else for a response. Survey information is used for much the same purposes.

**__**

**__****Personal information and choice  **

****

**You may choose whether to provide personal information online.**

Personal information is information about someone that can easily identify him or her. Personal information includes things like name, address and phone number. A domain name or IP address is not considered personal information. This site may request personal information to conduct surveys, send publications, or tell you of changes to PackageMapping.com web pages. In these cases, personal information is needed to answer your request.

Personal information about you is not collected unless you voluntarily provide it by sending an E-mail, participating in an online survey, or completing an on-line form. If you choose not to use these tools, you will still be able to browse the PackageMapping.com Internet site and read or download any information from it.

Any personally identifiable information is never made available for commercial use.  It is never sold, rented, or given out to any other party unless required by law.

**Our Policy Towards Children**

The Site is not directed to persons under 18\. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable information, we will delete such information from our files.

**__**

**__****Cookies and Applets**

PackageMapping.com might use cookies to store only non personal information.  Additionally, PackageMapping.com gathers information from outside sources that might use "cookies" to better serve their users. Cookies are simple text files stored on your computer by your web browser. They are temporary random identifiers that help personalize your browser session. Cookies do not contain personally identifying information and do not affect your privacy or security. You can refuse the cookie or delete the cookie file from your computer by using the method indicated when you access the application that uses cookies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information ( **not** including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google®, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

An applet is a subprogram that executes within another application, and can be sent along with a web page to a user to support certain functions, such as interactive animations, immediate calculations, or other simple tasks without having to access the host’s server. PackageMapping.com does not currently use applets.

**__**

**__****Security **

You are on a public Internet site and any information you send via this site may be accessed by others. PackageMapping.com uses current technology to protect any personal information provided through this web site. When you enter a secure area of this site you may be subject to authentication, monitoring and auditing. You have entered a secure area if you must enter a login name and password to enter. 

Unauthorized attempts to upload, change or destroy information on this site are strictly prohibited.. 

This information should not be construed in any way as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof, the security of information provided through any PackageMapping.com supported web site.

**__**

**__****Disclaimer **

Use of any portion of this site requires the respected owner's permission. 

The PackageMapping.com web site has links to many other Internet sites, including sites operated by government agencies, nonprofit organizations and private businesses. When you link to a site operated by a different organization, this Privacy Notice will not apply and you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site. Be aware that not all web sites have privacy notices and policies.

Links to external resources are provided as a public service, and do not imply endorsement by this site or its owner(s).

Neither PackageMapping.com nor its owner(s) warrants the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of any information published by this system, nor endorses any content, viewpoints, products, or services linked from this system, and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance on the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information. Portions of such information may be incorrect or not current. Any person or entity that relies on any information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk. 

PackageMapping.com and its owner(s) reserves the right to revise and update this Privacy Notice at any time by posting such revised Privacy Notice on the PackageMapping.com home page.

_****_

_****_**_Contact Information_**

> Any questions about the this privacy notice or comments about the PackageMapping.com Internet site should be directed to:
> 
> **Webmaster**  
>  PackageMapping.com  
>  Click here for contact information
